® Arun 's collections ®
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
( WOMAN SHRIEKS )
( FUNK MUSIC PLAYING )
My Purge playlist .
I put a lot of thought into it , especially this final tune
as it will be the last song you 'll ever hear .
Tough choice . ( BREATHING DEEPLY )
And then I thought , George Clinton !
The king of interplanetary funkmanship .
George 's psychedelic rock will leave you feeling funky , obviously .
And soulful , which is the least I can do .
Now , we played a lot of Purge games tonight , and we have just one more .
It 's simple , yet effective .
- It 's called " Mommy 's Choice . " - ( WHIMPERS )
Mommy , which one of you will survive this year 's Purge ?
( STRUGGLING )
( SCREAMING ) No ! No !
No !
( ALL CLAMORING )
MALE REPORTER : This is just one of a dozen protests around our capital
after reports emerged claiming that the New Founding Fathers
had been using the Purge to help their own economic agenda .
Here 's a recent statement by incendiary Purge detractor Dante Bishop .
For the past 20 years , the NFFA has taken to legalized murder
to decrease the poor population ,
which in turn keeps the government 's spending down .
Less welfare , less healthcare , less housing .
MALE REPORTER : Recent polling suggests that the growing anti-Purge sentiment
may have a monumental effect on the upcoming presidential election .
Establishment NFFA candidate Minister Edwidge Owens
has been losing ground to wildcard Independent candidate Senator Charlie Roan .
Eighteen years ago , Roan was forced to watch the brutal execution
of her entire family on Purge Night
and entered the political arena soon after with one goal in mind .
To put an end to the annual holiday .
I have no doubt that the soul of our country is at stake .
The Purge has to come to an end .
MALE REPORTER : Senator Roan is proving to be the greatest threat to the NFFA regime
since they first took office 25 years ago ...
( GLASS THUDS )
Is the cunt that close ?
All polls have her a point behind .
I 'm sorry , Caleb , I 've done ...
No sorrys , Minister , you 're doing a great job .
Let us put you where you need to be .
Thomas .
We have our people out there countering all this anti-NFFA bullshit .
What else can we do ?
( SHOUTING ) We do whatever it fucking takes !
I have had it with all these idealistic pigs .
They want the impossible . Everyone to have .
Some cannot have .
Not enough to go around .
It 's time to do something about all these cocksuckers ,
like that rat Bishop and the cunt Senator
trying to dismantle everything we 've built .
We are going to use this year 's Purge
to do some spring cleaning , gentlemen .
FEMALE MODERATOR : And where will you be spending Purge Night , Minister ?
I will once again be presiding over my party 's Midnight Purge Mass
because I still believe in it .
The Midnight Purge Mass ,
where our great NFFA leaders gather together and slaughter innocents .
Is murder our new religion ?
FEMALE MODERATOR : Senator .
Murder is our new religion . That 's snappy .
No , the Midnight Purge Mass where NFFA leaders gather to celebrate
the night that saved this country from economic ruin .
We have other ways .
Now , America is built upon sacrifice .
From the Revolution all the way to World War II .
Our Lord God sacrificed his only Son ...
Everybody look alive .
ERIC : Copy . We have eyes on her , boss .
MINISTER OWENS : That 's why we must sacrifice every year in order to rid ourselves of hatred .
Remember what I said . She moves , we move .
( AUDIENCE CHEERING )
Now , the stats are undeniable . There has been far less crime ...
( TAPPING PODIUM ) This is crap . Do I have to listen to this ?
Send me to the Principal 's office . I can 't listen to this anymore .
Okay , we 'll send you to the Principal 's office ' cause you can 't keep your mouth shut .
More low-income people are killed during the Purge than anyone else .
( SCATTERED CHATTER )
The money generated from the Purge lines the pockets of the NRA and insurance companies .
WOMAN : Don 't listen to her !
Any government system that relies on violence
to answer its problems must be rebooted .
She 's doing good , Leo .
( AUDIENCE CHEERING )
It is time to call upon the better angels of our nature .
He is going to keep lying .
Jesus Christ . There she goes again .
- Secure the audience . - I 'm on it .
- SENATOR ROAN : I 'd like to talk to you guys . - ( CHEERING CONTINUES )
Put a leash on her , Chief . She 's no good to anyone dead .
You got it , Leo .
- Okay . We 're on the move . - ERIC : Copy , boss .
Thank you very much . Thank you so much . Thank you .
Go sit down . I 'm happy to stay here for the rest of the night .
Stay close to her . Keep it tight .
Go out . Purge and purify . Purge and purify !
Hi . Thank you again .
MALE REPORTER : As she 's done many times before ,
Senator Roan broke security protocol ,
walking off the stage , stepping into the audience .
Tell you this much , she got ' em little titties ,
but she got some big-ass balls .
She ain 't got a snowball 's chance in a steam bath of winning this thing ,
but she be taking on them ol ' white-haired George Washington wannabe mofos
all by herself .
And to that , I say bully for her .
Oh , horseshit . She 's full of it too .
Nothing 'll ever change .
Hey , Laney . Laney , Laney ?
I think we 've offended Marcos with our anti-Senator talk .
The Senator 's going to win .
She 's gonna make real changes too . You 'll see .
All she needs is Florida .
She gets the 29 electoral votes from Florida , that puts her over 270 .
- She can do it . - JOE : Smartass .
All that useless shit and can 't butter a damn bagel correctly .
- I could butter your bagel , boss . - ( GASPS )
- Oh , you 'd butter my bagel ? - LANEY : Mmm ...
Well , you got jokes over there .
Yeah , you just be careful , kid , with all that hope , ' cause it can be a bad thing .
Hope can lead to a lot of letdown .
Tell him , Irish I.
Excuse me , what ?
I 'm not paying attention .
I 'm thinking about waffles and pussy .
That 's all I ever really think about , actually .
- Mmm-mmm ... - JOE : Irish I , ladies and gentlemen .
( ALL CHUCKLING )
The fuck you laughing at ? I 'm dead serious .
- Ah , fuck ! - ( LANEY LAUGHING )
The New Founding Fathers believe in fairness .
And we hear what the people are saying .
That the Purge benefits the rich and the powerful .
That was never the intention .
From this point on , no one is exempt .
The rules protecting level 10 government officials have been revoked .
Yeah . Come in .
You seeing this ?
Yeah , NFFA is revoking the Purge rule
that protects government officials of ranking 10 on Purge Night .
Yeah , I 'll secure a safe house and full security detail on the night .
No . I 'm staying home on Purge Night .
Senator , I don 't think that 's a good idea .
If the voters get wind that I 'm hiding in a fortress like some rich asshole ,
I lose votes and the NFFA wins .
I stay home like 99 % of the population .
Make it safe . Whatever it takes .
Right .
( HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING )
( SCREAMS )
( SINISTER LAUGHTER )
Half price on all masks .
Come on inside .
The Purge is Halloween for adults !
( SINISTER LAUGHTER )
Hordes of young adults are arriving from Spain , Denmark , South Africa .
They 're being called Murder Tourists as they are here for one reason .
To Purge .
We 're here to experience the Purge .
To kill . Release all the anger and hate .
To be like Americans . We 're very excited .
( SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE )
Foreigners coming to our capital to kill .
Murder tourism . It 's the new booming business in our country this year .
MRS. SABIAN : Murder tourism .
What 's happened to our country , Joe ?
Mrs. Sabian , I wish I knew .
But you take care of yourself , Mrs. S.
Next time you need something , just give us a call .
I 'll have Marcos run it over and save you the trip , okay ?
MRS. SABIAN : I come by to flirt with you , Joe !
What ?
MRS. SABIAN : No one 's gonna take that from me .
JOE : Ah , you better get out of here . Get on out of here .
( MRS. SABIAN CHUCKLING )
Yeah !
Oh . Get out of here .
Now she nasty .
She ... That 's a nasty woman , right there .
( PACKETS THUDDING )
( LAUGHING )
Joe . Mira .
Son of a bitch !
( DOOR BELL DINGING )
Where 's he going ? I never saw him move so damn fast .
All right , girls , give it up . I won 't have to call the police .
Get outta my face , old man !
Let 's not do this the hard way , okay ? I 'm giving you an out .
All right , give up the candy or I 'll have to take it away from you .
You touch me and I scream " rape , " you cocksucking pig .
Now walk away .
LANEY : Give it back .
Who are you , bitch ? Better get out of my way !
That 's Laney Rucker , Kimmy .
Laney Rucker ?
Holy shit .
( CHUCKLES )
OG Queen badass ?
Yo ! They called you Pequeña Muerte .
Little Death .
( LAUGHING )
Yo , you 're my motherfucking hero .
That makes me proud .
Now give back whatever you stole .
And apologize .
Oh , my God .
Sorry , mister . I was just playin ' .
So , Ms. Rucker , what happened to you ?
You look all whitish now .
Later , Ms. Rucker . Wish I met you back in the day .
Excuse me .
( GROANS )
Well ...
You were a lot more respectful back when you were shoplifting here .
- ( CHUCKLES ) - You know , I distinctly remember one time ,
you called me " sir . "
Oh , bullshit .
But listen , I just want to say thank you .
You 're my family , Joe .
I appreciate that . Thank you , Laney .
( CHUCKLES )
( CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO )
LEO : I want men in there .
I want men in there . I want a lot of men back there .
She 's got some security , but I 'm revamping the entire thing .
We got new barricades on all the doors , all the windows back and front .
CHIEF COUPER : Looks safe .
Chief , if you tell me it 's safe one more time , I 'm gonna throw you down the steps .
CHIEF COUPER : Please don 't do that .
Men here . Men here .
We got a security monitor system in this room .
We got eyes and ears on everything .
This is her safe room . She is not to leave her safe room .
No one is to go inside her safe room . Do we understand each other ?
This is a mess . She 's not gonna be happy about it .
I don 't care if she 's happy , Chief .
And I want to go on record as saying this is a bad idea .
No matter what we do here , this house and this Senator are at risk on Purge Night .
- You understand me ? - Duly noted .
Let 's lock it down .
" Let 's lock it down . "
It 's just me and you , pal .
Tell me what you want me to do . I 'm there .
Go downstairs , make sure they take care of the doors .
- Keep an eye on that guy . - Done .
BISHOP ON TV : The NFFA has created predatory capitalism
where profit-making is the essence of democracy .
( CELLPHONE RINGING )
We 've come to D.C. to make some changes .
FEMALE REPORTER : That was Dante Bishop . Like his predecessor Carmelo Johns ...
- ( PHONE BEEPS ) - Joe 's Deli .
... Dante is suspected of eliminating wealthy NFFA supporters on Purge Nights .
Excuse me ?
And many are wondering why he has come to Washington this year .
Wait , wait . Hold it . Wait a minute .
Why are you raising my rates now ? Today ?
Do you know what today is ?
Yeah , but look , I ... ( STUTTERING ) Yeah ... I can 't afford that .
What do you mean , you 're sorry ?
Yeah , I 'm talking to you . Let me speak to your ... Your super ...
- Son of a ... Son of a bitch ! - ( PHONE DROPS )
Joe ?
What the hell 's going on ?
JOE : The damn insurance company .
They just raised the premium on my Purge coverage . By thousands .
The day before the damn Purge .
If I don 't pay it by tomorrow , I have no Purge coverage for this store .
They can 't do that .
Yeah , well , they just did it .
Just lock the place down , Joe .
Yeah , but that 's not enough .
If I have no insurance , I am screwed .
( SIGHS )
I 'll just have to protect this place myself .
- Are you crazy ? - MARCOS : That 's not a good idea , boss .
Look , we love this place , too , Joe . I 've been coming here since I was born .
But it 's just stuff . It can be replaced .
You can 't be .
Yeah , but what about what you do on Purge Night , Laney ?
Huh ?
Is that not the pot calling the kettle brown ? No ?
That 's different , Joe , and you know that .
I 'm protected , and you won 't be .
This is all I got , guys . This is my slice of the pie .
( EXHALES )
Man , I cannot , I can 't lose this place .
I can 't lose this place .
Hold on , Joe . Let 's talk about this .
Everything is in place .
Team 's in position .
Ten minutes to lockdown , boss .
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
Hey , Mama .
( DOOR CLOSES )
You ready ?
Yeah .
Vaya con Dios .
Okay , let 's go .
Okay . This is gonna be home for the next 12 hours .
You need anything , you contact me and me only .
- Clear ? - Clear .
Let 's begin .
( BEEPING )
( SHUTTERS WHIRRING )
( WHIRRING STOPS )
( ALARM BLARING ON TV )
FEMALE VOICE ON TV : This is not a test .
This is your Emergency Broadcast System
announcing the commencement of the annual Purge sanctioned by the U.S. government .
Commencing at the siren , any and all crime , including murder ,
will be legal for 12 continuous hours .
Here we go .
Police , fire and emergency medical services
will be unavailable until tomorrow morning at 7 a.m.
And , for the first time since its inception ,
no one has been granted special immunity from the Purge .
No citizen or group will be exempt .
Blessed be our New Founding Fathers , and America , a nation reborn .
May God be with you all .
( SIREN BLARING )
- ( STATIC ) - I see you , Bobby .
( EXHALES ) You know you can relax now , right ?
No , I 'll relax in the morning .
Am I interrupting ?
Senator , you should be in the den .
Eric , thank you for being here tonight .
My pleasure .
Leo , have a drink with me .
You don 't have a choice .
Sounds serious .
Don 't say a word .
Or I 'll stick my foot up your ass .
( DRINK POURING )
( SIGHS )
Sit .
It 's water , Leo .
Are you scared ?
I 'm terrified .
What made you apply for this position ?
I like your politics .
No . No bullshit . I want a real answer .
I lost my son some years ago .
He was killed .
I almost did something on Purge Night that would 've destroyed a lot of lives .
I want this night gone .
I know you do , too .
Especially after what you lost .
Yeah . Despite all of that ,
you have a big problem with how I do things .
You take risks , Senator .
My job is to eliminate risks and keep you alive .
You don 't make that easy .
The soul of this country is at stake , Leo .
The only way that I can win is to risk everything , and that includes my life .
( EXHALES )
- ( MUSIC PLAYING ) - WOMAN : Peace , not Purge !
( LAUGHING ) You go , girls !
Have a drink on us !
LANEY : Can 't you see we 're working ?
PURGE PARTIER : Purge , motherfuckers !
( ALL SHOUTING )
Just gonna wait right here and see what happens .
PURGE PARTIER : Purge !
They probably won 't bother us , okay ?
- ( GRUNTING ) - ( GASPS )
( SOFTLY ) Purge . Purge . Purge .
Go , go , go ! Let 's move !
( MEN SHOUTING )
( MEN LAUGHING )
( WOMAN SCREAMING )
( WOMAN CRYING )
WOMAN : Help ! Help ! Please !
Somebody help ! Help ! Help !
( CONTINUES CRYING )
Please ! Please ! ( SCREAMS )
Stop ! Stop ! Please , stop !
Please , help him !
Something 's going down . Hey , looks like someone needs our services .
Let 's go . Let 's do this . Stop .
WOMAN : I shot my husband ! I shot him . Oh , God !
LANEY : Okay . Calm down . Tell me what happened .
( WOMAN CRYING )
Oh , no ! It was a mistake ! I 'm sorry !
( MAN SCREAMING IN DISTANCE )
( JOE EXHALES )
MARCOS : Hey , boss ! It 's me ! It 's me .
Come on outta there , boy .
Good Lord , son .
It 's Purge Night . You don 't sneak up on black people .
( SIGHS ) Good night , blue cheese .
Where the hell you going ? And why you carrying a chair ?
I like sitting .
Yeah , well , you ain 't gonna be staying .
Look , you know I appreciate you coming out here to watch my back , but I 'm good .
- I got this . - No .
( PANTING ) I 'll stay . Nothing else to do .
Look , please don 't be a pain in the ass .
I want you to go home and be safe .
I don 't want you out here on Purge Night , son . I got this !
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( HORN HONKING )
- ( POP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO ) - ( SCREECHING CONTINUES )
( GIRLS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
( LAUGHING )
KIMMY : Purge Night , bitch ! It 's Purge Night , bitch ! It 's Purge Night , bitch !
Give me that shit . Let 's go !
Fuck you !
( POP MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING )
Ooh !
( LAUGHING )
Happy Purge , you old fuck !
You better find someplace else to go !
I got a wicked sweet tooth tonight .
And I want my candy bar .
And I 'm gonna take it .
You don 't got the balls to stop me . ( LAUGHING )
( SHRIEKS ) Fuck !
MARCOS : I have the balls .
Now go .
I already took care of my mom and dad tonight .
You 're next .
I want my candy bar , cocksucker .
( GASPING )
Come on !
( CAR DOOR CLOSING )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
So , what 's up with that ?
Every day in Juárez was like the Purge .
I know how to shoot , boss .
Son , I really wish you 'd stayed home .
( CANS CLANKING )
( CANS OPENING )
- I don 't know . - It 's that time .
Eric .
What are you still doing up here ? You 're on first floor duty .
How was your chat ?
Enlightening . Go .
Chief , find a bedroom . I got it from here .
All right , Leo .
Boys . Why don 't you take a break ?
Go watch some TV , huh ? It 's gonna be a long night .
Yes , sir .
( SILENCED GUNSHOTS )
( STATIC )
I 'm coming outside , boys .
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( BEEPING )
( WHIRRING )
How ya doing out there , Bobby ?
Sniper One , radio check .
Bobby , radio check .
Sniper Two , radio check .
Sniper Two .
( SILENCED GUNSHOTS )
( DOOR OPENING )
Someone is coming for you .
- What ? - Put that on .
- Leo , the house is surrounded ... - Move , move !
I 'm moving . What are you ...
You said you had men on the roof . You have snipers .
- Not anymore . Not anymore . - What do you mean , not anymore ?
- Someone betrayed us . - What ?
- I can 't trust anyone . Put on that vest . - ( BEEPING )
Listen to me ! This isn 't a drill .
Someone 's coming to kill you . You understand me ?
Move .
SENATOR ROAN : Moving .
- What the ... - Go !
Okay , what the hell is that ?
That 's my little secret . Move .
One , two , three !
SENATOR ROAN : Okay .
( BEEPING )
ERIC : Boss ! It 's just me !
Fuck .
- Where the hell is she ? - Jesus Christ .
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( SCREAMS )
( GRUNTS )
- What the fuck is this ? - ( BEEPING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO )
I don 't know what the fuck that is .
( STATIC )
Our mark may be outside . Repeat .
Your mark may be outside .
Check your perimeters .
( SIGHS )
No payment unless we find her .
Fuck .
I see her !
( GUNSHOTS )
( BEEPING )
Down !
LEO : ( PANTING ) Come here .
Move . Go ! Go ! Go ! Go !
( GUNSHOTS )
Hey , Joe , you up there ?
Is that Laney ?
Marcos !
My guys ! How you all doing tonight ?
We 're good . You ?
Ah ... ( SIGHS )
I just dropped someone off at triage .
His wife shot him because she couldn 't stand looking at his face anymore .
She said Purging didn 't make her feel any better like they said it would .
Just stay safe , Lane .
Anything happens , do not hesitate to call us .
Yeah , same goes for you .
- Okay ? - All right .
All right .
( VAN DRIVING AWAY )
God , I hate that she 's out there like that .
WOMAN : ( SCREAMING ) Help me ! Help me !
LEO : Stop . Stop !
( BOTH PANTING )
What was that ? Some kind of homegrown militia ?
Those were skilled mercs with a lot of money behind them .
Enough to get to someone on our staff .
I 'm guessing it 's the Minister .
The Minister , the NFFA , the whole fucking lot of them .
I 'm getting too close .
( LEO PANTING )
It 's a lot of blood , Leo . We should call someone .
I don 't know who to trust . We are on our own . You understand me ?
Okay . Where do we go ?
East . Out of the city . There are a lot of threats .
( EXHALES )
There 's a lot of death .
( VEHICLE APPROACHING )
MAN : Purge Sanitation Services .
Death collection haul .
Purge victim removal and disposal .
Keep Washington clean .
It 's okay .
Death collection haul .
This is how it 's gonna go now .
Like you said , fate of the country 's at stake .
Okay ? It 's my show now .
Look , I 'm not an idiot .
I know what you 're capable of . I 'm the one who hired you .
But if I see something I don 't like , I 'm not gonna be quiet about it .
It 's not in my nature .
( BREATHING DEEPLY ) Senator , I need you to follow me .
( SHOUTING IN DISTANCE )
Come on .
( MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY OVER DRONE )
It 's Tommy , sir .
He 's in bad shape . He 's unconscious .
Everyone else up there is dead .
Get him to the ground unit . Get him stabilized .
Then start street surveillance . I 'll search from above .
We need her alive , so let 's find her before the crazies do .
Sir .
( MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY OVER DRONE )
They 're tracking us .
Where ? I 'm not seeing them . How are they seeing us ?
Mercenaries ?
No . That 's a homemade drone . Purgers .
( MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY OVER DRONE )
SENATOR ROAN : Now what ?
Run . Fast .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES OVER DRONE )
Come , come , come !
It 's behind you , Leo . Thirty-five yards back , 15 yards up .
( BOTH PANTING )
- ( SCREAMING ) - ( GUNSHOT )
( ALL GRUNTING )
- Down ! - ( GUNSHOT )
( SCREAMS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( ELECTRICITY CRACKLING )
Reason I 'm so hard on you , son , like I am is
someday I 'd like to make you a partner .
Yep . Oh , boy . Coming here from another country like you did .
Having your own business .
American dream is still alive .
( MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
WOMAN : Whoo-hoo !
( PURGERS SPEAKING RUSSIAN )
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
We love you , America . America is the greatest country in the world .
WOMAN : We are gonna kill you .
( ALL CLAMORING )
( SPEAKING RUSSIAN )
We will now Purge .
- We will torture you and violate your flesh . - ( GRUNTING )
Remove your skin and share in your blood .
This is the American way .
( GUNSHOTS )
JOE : Senator .
Come with us .
( SHUTTERS OPENING )
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa ...
( EXHALES )
- Stay . - Yeah .
Yeah .
( EXHALES )
JOE : Well , this is my place .
You can stay all night if you want to .
Now , I got to ask you 'cause I 'm just a nosey old dog .
What in the Mississippi fuck was you doing outside on Purge Night , Senator ?
( BREATHING DEEPLY ) Yeah .
There was an assassination attempt on me .
I can 't thank you enough , Mr ... I 'm sorry , I know you told me .
- Dixon . You can call me Joe , Senator . - Yeah .
Joe , I 'm Charlie .
- Charlie . - Yeah .
That 's Marcos right there .
Marcos is ... He 's a fan of yours .
- Hi , Marcos . - Hey , Senator .
- He actually think you can win this thing . - Oh , yeah ?
( LAUGHS ) Shit ! Tell her what she need to do to win , Marcos .
No , it 's not my place to say .
Well , you saved my life , Marcos . I 'd like to hear it , please .
Florida is the key .
You have to get the elders .
That 's smart .
He 's not wrong , Joe . What do you think ?
I don 't think you got a damn chance .
Well , have a little faith .
Well , I lost my faith in the system a long time ago , Senator . Water ?
Thank you .
Place is moderately secure . Cameras . Maybe we stay here .
" Maybe we stay here " ? Where you going ? You going back out there ?
Joe , do you have a first aid kit ? Leo , my security , was shot .
- I 'm fine . - You 're not fine .
- I 'm fine . - You 're not . Sit .
You want me to take it off ?
( SIGHS )
It 's okay . It 's nothing .
Yeah ? Doesn 't look like nothing .
( GROANS ) Let me see . Let me see .
I know a little bit about first aid . I could help you .
The bullet 's deep .
- You need stitches . - Yeah .
But we can 't do that here .
Right . Clean it up . Patch it up . Come on . Move .
Okay .
Fast . Come on .
( LEO WINCING )
What about you guys ? Who are you ?
- Is this necessary ? - It 's very necessary .
You , what 's your name ? Where you from ?
Marcos Dali . Mexico City .
But I 've been an American citizen for two years .
You got a record ?
Not here .
What did you do in Mexico ?
I tried to survive .
What are you doing out on Purge Night ?
Protecting the deli against looters because my boss lost his Purge insurance yesterday .
Yeah , that 's something you can look into , Senator .
Insurance companies screwing the working man .
Yeah ?
What 's your name , pal ?
You know what , Mr. Secret Service Man ?
You should be thanking my black ass for helping you instead of interrogating me .
SENATOR ROAN : His name is Joe Dixon .
- LEO : Joe Dixon , have I offended you ? - JOE : Yeah .
Yeah , man , just a little bit .
Your feelings are not a concern of mine .
Little respect . That 's all I need .
Everyone shut up , please !
- SENATOR ROAN : What ? - Look .
( LAUGHTER )
KIMMY : You stupid motherfucker !
You should have let us take the candy bar !
Now , you 're gonna fuckin ' pay for it , you stupid son of a bitch !
Whoo !
It 's a good night to Purge , isn 't it ?
Oh , hell !
Who the hell is that ?
The looters I was telling you about .
Purge Night , Senator . What did you expect ?
( KIMMY SCREAMS )
Hey , you old fuck ! I 'm back .
And I brought some friends .
And I 'm gonna get that candy bar .
They have chainsaws and they 're coming inside .
All right . I got to get you outta here .
Yeah , but they 're at both entrances .
Then I 'm gonna Purge by killing you and burning this bitch to the ground !
I gotta call her .
Who ?
We have a friend out there in a triage van .
You trust this friend ?
Hey , you still questioning my integrity .
Boy , you are a piece of work , man .
( SIGHS ) Come on , girl , pick up .
RONDO : Those motherfuckers blindsided us , man .
- I gotta get back out there . - No , no , no .
You 're not going anywhere . I told your mom I 'd look after you .
Just hurry up . Hurry up and bandage me up so I can get back out there .
Okay , you promised me you were gonna stay home tonight .
Well , I want to Purge tonight .
- No . - I want to Purge .
Laney , what ? Laney !
( BREATHING DEEPLY ) For real , Laney ?
Yeah . For real .
You heard me right . Senator Roan .
Call me back , Lane . We need you bad .
- ( GIRLS SHOUTING OUTSIDE ) - ( SIGHS )
She 'll call back .
We can 't count on your friend . These kids will be in here soon .
What do we do ?
Okay .
We 're gonna work as a team to protect this woman .
You gentlemen understand what 's at stake here , yes ?
- Yes ? All right . - Yes .
( SINGING ) We are gonna Purge today
Purge today , Purge today
We are gonna Purge today Burn this bitch down
Fuck !
Okay , you take the back , I 'm gonna take the front .
I 'll take the front with you .
No , you 're not gonna be on the frontline .
Are you crazy , Leo ? Give me a gun .
I will give you a gun , but you 're not on the frontline . Over my dead body .
Then you better drop dead .
JOE : I think he 's right , Senator .
Thank you , Deli Man .
Deli Man ? I agree with you , you still throwing attitude ?
Okay , enough ! Executive decision .
I 'm with Leo . We need as many guns as we can get .
( WHIRRING )
Go , go , go !
Move , move , move !
Down .
Just point and shoot . Do not shoot me .
( WHIRRING CONTINUES )
KIMMY : If I want some candy , I 'll take some candy !
I 'll take whatever the fuck I want !
My mom 's not gonna like this !
KIMMY : This is what the Purge is all about . Me getting mine .
You getting yours and nobody stopping anybody !
Bye-bye , motherfucker !
Say goodnight , cocksucker . Because here comes your candy girl !
Here they come .
- ( ALL LAUGHING ) - BIKINI GIRL : Fucking asshole !
( LAUGHING )
Hold on !
( TIRES SCREECHING )
Wait here .
( COCKING )
- ( YELLING ) - ( COCKING GUN )
Pequeña Muerte is back , bitches .
( BANGING )
LANEY : Hey , guys ! I got your message .
Laney !
- This is our girl . - Go , go , go !
Holy shit , it really is you .
- Where do we go ? - The van .
LEO : Go .
LANEY : Come on , Joe .
I 'll be with you in a minute . I 'll be there .
( WHIRRING )
( SIGHS )
Joe , come on .
You get out of here , kid . I 'm staying .
They 'll kill you .
JOE : Go now !
If you stay , I stay .
Just leave .
Joe , listen to me .
For some reason , the Senator ended up in our neighborhood , in your deli .
Maybe it 's our duty to help protect her .
We 'll rebuild the deli . Whatever it takes , you and me . I promise .
LANEY : Come on , guys . Now !
Where we headed ?
Underground triage center service in the community .
It 's completely secure .
( INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO )
Expand our perimeter . They 're on foot . They can 't be far .
MERC : Earl , spoke with the ground unit .
Tommy regained consciousness .
Says he got a shot off at the Senator 's security .
He thinks the bullet is lodged in his shoulder .
( CHUCKLES )
( SQUELCHING )
( YELLING )
How the hell did it get to this ?
( CLEARS THROAT )
Who is he ?
Why is he cuffed ?
Rondo . Two bullet holes delivered by a rival gang , but he 's a good kid .
He 's chained up because I didn 't want him Purging anymore .
So , Senator ...
NFFA made a move on your ass .
Seems that way .
Goddamn conniving , duplicitous , crooked , cocksucking politicians .
Agreed .
We 're not all that bad .
My experience , Senator ?
My people are on our own , no matter what you all say or promise .
I 'm kinda confused here . Who the hell is this lady ?
( SCOFFS )
You big dope !
You give people from the neighborhood a bad name .
( GUNSHOTS )
LEO : Just some Purgers .
That 's crossfire .
Not for us .
You seem really close .
How do you know each other ?
Joe gave me a job seven years ago when I first came here from Mexico .
I 've been working for him ever since .
And you ?
Joe 's been looking out for me since I was a kid .
And he helped me get out of the life .
Sounds like Joe is a saint .
Yeah , well , I ain 't no saint .
I 'm just doing my part .
Riding around in a van , on Purge Night , helping people ?
It 's pretty dangerous .
Unwritten Purge rule is leave the triage units alone .
It 's true , for the most part .
Seriously , Laney , who the hell are these people ?
- LANEY : ( LAUGHING ) Do you read ? - ( GUNSHOTS )
LEO : Down ! Everybody down !
Anybody hit ?
SENATOR ROAN : I 'm okay . I 'm okay . I 'm okay .
- You sure ? - Yes .
- JOE : Laney ! - I 'm okay .
Oh , Jesus Christ ! Rondo is dead .
( GRUNTS ) What the fuck was that ?
- They found us , Senator . - ( HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING )
I want you to turn left ! Go under the freeway .
- Move ! Move ! - Yes .
MAN : Tonight , the gates of hell will open and invite me in .
It 's survival of the fucking fittest .
Who 's the fittest ?
I 'm the fittest of them all !
What the fuck ? We 're gonna lose them under there .
Ground unit , get your asses moving and get here now . We got them cornered .
( ALL YELLING )
( METAL CLANGING )
( ROARING )
Turn here and stop .
( YELLING CONTINUES )
Do we just wait here ?
No , they 'll have units on the ground . They 're gonna be all over us .
We all better figure it out fast 'cause I don 't like it here .
SENATOR ROAN : It doesn 't make any sense .
There was no way they could 've known we 'd be in this van .
Doesn 't matter . They did .
You son of a bitch .
Leo ?
- Leo ? - Move .
- ( WINCES ) - Leo .
( LEO MOANS )
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
SENATOR ROAN : Oh !
Leo , what the hell are you doing ?
Leo , what ...
( GRUNTING )
( SENATOR ROAN GASPS )
Trace bullet . That 's how he found us .
Just leave it here and drive away .
They 'll never know we left here .
Yeah , well , I wish it were that simple . You all need to see this .
There 's a whole bunch of negroes coming right this way .
And we sitting up here like a bucket of motherfucking chicken .
( COCKING )
( BEEPING )
What 's your ETA ?
Two minutes , Earl .
MAN : Open the door , now !
( ALL CLAMORING )
What are we gonna do ?
They 'll start blasting if we move .
They 'll start blasting if we don 't .
Open the door ! Open the door , now !
MAN : Open the goddamn doors !
What 's the plan ?
( ALL SHOUTING )
( WHISTLING )
MAN : Yo , yo , yo ! Quiet down ! Quiet down !
- What the hell is that ? - MAN : Quiet down !
MAN : I know what I heard . I know what I heard .
( MAN WHISTLING )
I told you I ain 't no saint . Everybody 's got a past .
That was a Crip whistle . They just threw it back .
If this is the right set , we should be good .
MAN : I know , I know what I heard . I know .
All right .
We 're not gonna hurt you . Just help my fuckin ' boy . He 's gonna die .
We help you , you do something for us .
( BEEPING CONTINUES )
They 're still under the overpass , but they 're on the move .
Get your asses in there .
( BEEPING )
They stopped . Stop the truck .
We 're going on foot .
( BEEPING CONTINUES )
( BEEPING RAPIDLY )
Clear !
( BEEPING STOPS )
Earl , we found the trace bullet , but no sign of the target .
- Yeah , we 're heading back . - ( WHISTLING )
Ground unit , come in .
- Come in , I need a fuckin ' sitrep . - ( GUNSHOTS )
( GANG MEMBER LAUGHING )
GANG MEMBER ON RADIO : Fuck you , motherfucker !
No one following .
We 're clear .
DAWN : We 're a few blocks away .
I 'm gonna call in and tell them we have a special guest .
Where are we ?
You 'll see .
( MEN CHATTERING )
What is this place ?
We call this a Safe Zone .
- Senator , Dante Bishop . - Mr. Bishop .
This is Angel .
Dawn called . Told me you guys were coming through .
So the NFFA came at you tonight ?
Can 't say I 'm surprised .
Let me show you around , get you settled in .
You set all this up , Mr. Bishop ?
Yes , this is my organization .
We have doctors , and nurses , EMTs , paramedics .
This is their way of protesting this damn night .
LEO : How many people know about this place ?
Just the volunteers , and the homeless that we invite in .
Look , these are the real victims of the Purge .
The people that the NFFA are trying to eliminate
so that they don 't have to take care of them anymore .
These men that are armed , you 'll have them at all the entrances and the rooftop ?
Yes . My men will keep you safe .
Or as safe as you can be on Purge Night .
Appreciate it .
- Mr. Bishop . - Yeah .
Thank you , for all of this . I am impressed .
Well , don 't thank me . Thank the volunteers .
Mr. Bishop , I 've heard stories
of tactics that you employ on Purge Night .
I can 't say that I agree with any of it .
I 'll tell you what .
You get elected , you stop this night ,
and I don 't have to do what I do anymore .
Let 's go , Angel .
Fair enough .
BISHOP : You hold down the fort here .
Keep an eye on her . And keep her and her people quiet . Okay ?
All right , let 's go !
I want access to every surveillance camera in the city .
We 'll do a grid search for that fucking triage van .
It 's out there somewhere . Find it .
Yeah .
Your crew ? Your guys ? They feel like family ?
Boss .
We did the right thing .
Yeah .
But it 's time to go .
Gotta get back to the deli .
What ? No . Are you fucking crazy ? We 're safe here .
Laney , you know I 'll walk back if I have to .
Fine . I 'll drive you .
But if we run into any problems , we 're coming right back here .
Deal .
SENATOR ROAN : Really ? Can you do that ?
We 'll see her again , Marcos .
And she 's safe here .
Let 's hit it .
I don 't know , but I bet it was really cool . ( LAUGHS )
It is , it is .
- Hey , you okay ? - Yeah , I 'm okay .
Good .
- I 'm gonna go take a look around . - Okay .
Stay here .
Okay , boss .
What are you doing here ?
- Hand . - Why are you here ?
( GRUNTING )
( CLATTERING )
What the hell 's going on here ?
- He was snooping around ! - Hey , hey ! Okay , okay , okay .
- Hey ! Hey . - It 's all right . It 's all right .
- Red , back up . It 's okay . - ( MAN CHOKING )
Just put the gun down , all right ? Everybody 's okay .
Back up .
We 're okay .
All right ? All right ?
We 're good . It 's all good , okay ?
I 'm just getting my weapon .
What 's going on ?
Just doing my job .
Senator , it 's just a misunderstanding .
Why don 't we go back outside ?
Come on .
- SENATOR ROAN : Are you seeing this , Leo ? - LEO : Yes , Senator .
Senator , why don 't we go outside ...
Stop .
Those are the Minister 's biggest financial supporters .
The NFFA .
Our Lady of Sorrows .
Is that where the Minister is going to be tonight for the Purge Mass ?
- We believe so . - You believe ... ( SCOFFS )
What is all this ?
Why do you have all this ?
You 're gonna assassinate him .
You 're gonna assassinate the Minister tonight , aren 't you ?
You know , somebody 's got to say it out loud .
What in the fuck happened tonight ?
Nobody 's gonna believe it .
Mmm-hmm .
Irish Ike 's gonna be like , " Bullshit .
- " Now where 's my waffles and pussy ? " - " ... and pussy ? "
( ALL LAUGHING )
He got that one-track mind .
That boy done lost his mind .
Shit .
I hope he 's okay tonight .
Yeah .
Hold on , guys . Look .
Those are government trucks .
I saw them on YouTube from last year 's Purge .
And they 're going straight back towards the Safe Zone .
You cannot do this . I need to win this thing fair and fucking square .
They are not playing fair and fucking square and neither should we .
This church will be locked up like Fort Knox .
You 'll never get through . You 're gonna get slaughtered .
Four churches were built on that site .
The original by your boy George Washington over 200 years ago .
The man liked to have escape tunnels attached to all his structures .
They 're all over D.C.
The tunnel under the original church has been closed up since the ' 50s .
But we reopened it .
We 're gonna walk right through there
and into that church without anybody even knowing it .
The original Founding Fathers are about to fuck over the New Founding Fathers .
Now how you like that for irony ?
How do you know where this mass is gonna be ?
Because we do whatever it takes . We did this for you , Senator .
No , it 's not for me . Get your boss on the phone . I need to talk to him .
- He 's not here . - Angel , listen to me .
You call him .
You tell him he does this and the Minister becomes a martyr .
I cannot have my presidency built on murder . You see that .
He will not leave this to the voters .
He does not believe in the American system .
Angel , believe in me . I can make this happen .
We do . That 's why we 're trying to pave a way for you
to the White House so you can make changes .
SENATOR ROAN : You 're gonna cost me the White House .
It 's Laney . She says there 's trucks approaching us .
What ?
Who is that ?
Government soldiers .
That 's the NFFA eliminating all their enemies this year .
They 're here for Bishop , but they will kill you .
- You need to evacuate your people . - We can 't move the injured .
- I need to get her out of here now . - There 's a way out back .
LEO : Where does it come out ?
The alleyway down to Third and Thompson .
LEO : Third and Thompson . Give me the phone .
Laney , I need you at Third and Thompson now .
Yeah , we 'll meet you there .
( TIRES SCREECHING )
So , we 're driving right back into that war zone ?
Stupid !
( ALL CHATTERING )
All these people .
We 'll protect them .
Please , stop the assassination .
- It 's too late . Now go . Stay safe . - Go !
So what we supposed to be , like some superheroes or something ?
That ain 't what I do .
I hate this night !
Ah , shit . Hell with it . Come on . Shit .
Let 's do it . Let 's go get ' em .
I can 't believe we 're outside again .
I 'm gonna get you through this .
( WIRE TWANGING )
( MAN EXCLAIMING )
MAN 1 : My God , it 's so close !
MAN 2 : At your own risk now ! ( LAUGHING )
Are you fucking kidding me ?
- Ready ? - Yeah .
- One . - MAN 2 : Go for it !
- Two . - MAN 1 : Try your luck !
Go !
( MEN MOANING )
MAN 2 : Good luck out there !
( SINGING ) Let me hear you whisper
That you love me too
Keep the love-light glowing in your eyes so true
JOE : Let 's go , let 's go !
Come on , I got you .
- LANEY : You guys okay ? - LEO : Yeah .
SENATOR ROAN : Thank you . Again .
LANEY : Where we headed ?
Drive . Out of this city . Get us out of here .
( BREATHING DEEPLY )
You okay , Senator ?
No , Marcos . I 'm not .
This night corrupts everyone .
- Senator . - I can 't win like this .
It goes against everything that I believe in .
We need to focus on one thing right now and that 's survival .
I need to make sure you get through this night .
I have to stop them from killing the Minister .
What ?
If they assassinate him , he becomes a martyr . We lose .
Yeah . And how do we do that ?
I don 't know . We have to do something .
Do what ? Do what ? You 're willing to risk your life to save an assassin ...
( THUDDING )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( LEO GROANS )
( PANTING )
( GRUNTING )
LEO : Everybody all right ?
LANEY : Joe , you okay ?
JOE : ( GROANING ) I 'll be okay .
SENATOR ROAN : Leo !
LEO : Gun ! ( GRUNTS )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( MAGAZINE CLATTERS )
( LANEY GASPING )
I know where they 're taking her . I know why she 's still alive .
Where ?
You find a safe place to hide and you stay there .
No . No way .
Whatever it is you plan on doing , we 're coming with you .
Let 's go .
( SCREAMING )
( MUFFLED GRUNTS )
( CONTINUES GRUNTING )
CHOIR : May the Purge protect us . Keep us pure .
Purge and purify .
May the Purge cleanse us . Keep us pure .
Come on , guys , that 's enough .
We 're getting paid to deliver the package , not gift-wrap it .
Come on , let 's go find a place to wait out the rest of this fucking night , huh .
( MUFFLED MOANS )
MINISTER OWENS : As we always do .
ALL : Blessed be the New Founding Fathers
for letting us Purge and cleanse our souls .
Blessed be America , a nation reborn .
Well , it 's been a long journey
to get away from the lies and the self-deception
to this place of knowledge and awareness of who we really are .
People of flesh , immensely flawed .
It 's hard to see the ugly truth .
But change can only come from acceptance .
And change we must , as it is our godly duty
to get rid of the fury and the hatred
that poisons our souls , makes us sick .
Makes us ugly .
Tonight ,
we , the leaders of this great country ,
will sin , scour , sanitize and sterilize our souls
until we are free again , and this country will be better for it .
We are not hypocrites !
We practice what we preach .
Purge and purify ! Say it with me .
ALL : Purge and purify ! Purge and purify !
Purge and purify ! Purge and purify !
Purge and purify !
Let us begin .
All right , look , it 's after midnight . We need to move .
I need a four-man team in there .
I need three with me . Got it ? Go !
LEO : Bishop !
Bishop !
I 'm unarmed .
How well do you know this Dante ?
Not well . So keep your eye on him .
JOE : Our boy is gonna get himself killed .
LEO : I 'm unarmed .
You know this lunatic , Dante ?
Yeah . I do .
Guns down .
What the hell are you doing here ?
Trying to get yourself killed ?
Is that the tunnel for the cathedral ?
How the fuck do you know about the tunnel ?
I asked you a question .
This is no longer an assassination . This is a rescue mission .
MINISTER OWENS : Jesus died for their sins .
( MUMBLING )
And now , our modern-day martyrs will die for our trespasses .
Our martyr 's name is Lawrence .
A lifelong drug addict . He wants to make amends .
He wants to serve his God and his government .
Let 's thank Lawrence for his gift .
ALL : Thank you , Lawrence .
- Thank you for your gift , Lawrence . - Thank you very much , Lawrence .
We love you , Lawrence .
( SHUDDERING )
These weapons have been cleansed with holy water ,
and they are now instruments of destruction .
( GRUNTING ) Fuck !
You all know the loyal Harmon James .
Worked with the NFFA tirelessly for many years .
Harmon will be the first Purger of the evening .
LAWRENCE : I 'm sorry . No , no , no . Please , please , please , please . No , no , no .
Please , no , no ! I 'm sorry ! No , please !
No ! I 'm sorry ! Please , no , no !
Please , no !
Please ! No ! Please , please !
- I 'm sorry ! - Release , Harmon .
No !
SENATOR ROAN : No !
( SQUELCHING )
Release the violence from your darkened heart !
Scour your soul . Let the light in .
You are blood-baptized .
And you are born again !
( BOTH GASPING )
His light entered your heart , Harmon .
Yeah . ( LAUGHS )
The power of Purging !
ALL : Purge and purify !
Purge and purify !
Purge and purify ! Purge and purify !
JOE : Psst .
No matter what happens , we stay together .
All right , this takes us to the mechanical room .
From there , we can access the cathedral .
( GRUNTS )
Stay there . Where do we go ?
The church is above us . So are 50 Secret Service agents .
You 're gonna take the staircase to the balcony .
Me and my guys , we 're gonna enter from behind the altar and this side here .
Okay , good . Let 's go get our girl , yeah ?
Before we get to our communal Purge , the Holy Horde of Many Martyrs ,
I 'd like to introduce a guest
who 's going to be the centerpiece of a very special Purge ceremony tonight .
This person
has threatened to dismantle everything
that we , New Founding Fathers , have done .
We must rid ourselves
of the negative emotions that she has stirred inside .
We must stop her from poisoning our great country
by taking away our freedoms .
- Yes ! - ( APPLAUSE )
I would like all the Founding Fathers to come to the altar .
Join me , brothers ,
as we eliminate evil
and Purge as one .
( SINGING ) There is a fountain filled with blood
Drawn from Immanuel 's veins
And sinners , plunged beneath that flood
Lose all their guilty stains
( SINGING CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY )
Lord of Air , Lord of Earth ,
we ask that you receive this child into your loving arms .
We are sinners .
Let us release .
Caleb , our leader ,
I invite you , sir , to lead us in this Purging
as you have and as you will .
Blessed be our New Founding Fathers for letting us Purge .
( BOTH GRUNTING )
Blessed be America , a nation reborn .
Rifle !
- ( ALL SCREAMING ) - ( GUNSHOTS FIRING )
She 's alive .
Down !
( GUNFIRE STOPS )
BISHOP : Where you all at ?
The hell are you all doing up there ?
Bring your asses down here .
( LAUGHING )
My negro .
Let 's go .
- Thank you . - MAN : I got you . I got you .
Hi .
- You okay ? - Yeah .
Thank you . Again .
( GUNSHOTS )
What was that ?
My men taking care of business . Go cover me .
We 're headed out . Back exit . We have her .
MAN : And we have him .
Move .
Hey !
- SENATOR ROAN : Listen to me . - BISHOP : Get off of me .
- Mr. Bishop . Please . - LEO : Watch our backs .
Just take a second and listen to me .
- BISHOP : It 's on our way to the exit . - I can win without this .
- SENATOR ROAN : Please ! - Cover our backs .
BISHOP : You will win . I 'm gonna make sure that happens .
- Open up ! - Stop .
This is murder . If you do this , you will be no different than them .
Get her .
LEO : Nope ! Don 't .
Listen to her .
She knows what she 's doing .
We don 't need to do this .
MAN : Hang on , Dante .
Get the fuck out of my way .
Wait , please !
( PANTING )
Don 't do this .
If you do this , you will be no different than them .
We can 't be like them .
Look at me .
( SOFTLY ) Purge , my son .
Purge .
It 's your right as an American .
Kill me . Kill me .
Purge .
You 're a son of God .
- God wants you to Purge . - Shut the fuck up !
Coward .
Purge !
Do it ! Do it ! Yes ! Yes !
Kill me !
Now , I 'm gonna tell you right now , I like black people ,
but I ain 't gonna let you all shoot these white folks .
These are our white people .
Okay ?
So , let 's put ' em down .
( SHUDDERING )
You better fucking win .
Go . Go .
Move !
Oh , my God .
You murderous pig .
I am gonna beat the shit out of you on election day .
I 'm not as politically correct as the Senator .
( GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
Good night , blue cheese .
Well played , Leo .
Thanks , Joe .
Come on , man .
- No , I 'm not gonna hurt you . - ( MUFFLED MOANING )
We have to get you out of there .
- BISHOP : Stay here , we 'll find a vehicle . - SENATOR ROAN : What about these people ?
Back , back , back ! Get back !
- LEO : You got this . - You know I got this .
- How bad is it ? - Not good .
Look , I got one more move in me . Cover me . Go !
( SCREECHING )
( EXCLAIMING )
Shh ! Be quiet !
Shut him up before he draws the wrong kind of attention .
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
You motherfucker !
( GRUNTING )
Get up .
( GRUNTS )
Motherfucker .
- Okay . No , it 's okay . You 're safe . - Thank you .
I gotta get the fuck outta here ! Let me out ! Let me out !
SENATOR ROAN : Stop him !
( GRUNTS )
( GUN COCKING )
( GROANS )
Joe !
Joe ?
You 're gonna be okay , Joe . Come on .
We gotta get you somewhere , okay ?
You 're gonna be okay . I promise you .
There 's nowhere to take me .
You 're gonna be fine . That 's what 's important .
She 's gonna make sure of it . Right , Senator ?
Yeah .
You got this .
I got this .
( GASPS )
Marcos ...
MARCOS : Joe , Joe , Joe .
Breathe , Joe , breathe .
( SOBBING ) No .
LANEY : Wake up , Joe . Wake up !
( SOBBING ) Joe !
MALE REPORTER : That was Senator Roan this morning , casting the first vote of the day .
It 's been a great day for the senator so far ,
having already won New York , California , and ...
Wait , hold on , I am getting word , right now ,
that the Senator has also taken Florida ,
which puts her well over the 270 electoral votes for the win .
So that is it .
It is now official , the next President of the United States will be Charlie Roan .
And President-elect Roan has already stated that her first order of business
will be taking executive action to put an end to the Purge .
LANEY : Updates ?
It 's a landslide .
All right , I 'll come by tomorrow . We can get started on the ceiling .
Sounds good .
This place is really coming along , Marcos .
Joe would be really happy .
I 'll catch you later , kid .
MALE REPORTER : We 're just now hearing reports
about a few scattered incidents around the country
where NFFA supporters are reacting violently to this defeat .
They are burning cars , breaking windows , looting , attacking police officers ...
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )